Guide to the Mix Collection, 1970-2014 (Bulk 1987-2001) MSS.143
Fales Library and Special Collections
- SERIES VII: 1993, 119145
  - Subseries G: Media, 119171
    - Title: [1.]--Against The Inhuman Undershadow of the Lynch Mob [2.]--Goblin Market [3.]--The Last Time [PAL], [1.]--Screened: 1993; 119325 (Box 93, Folder ID: 143.1103)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6500
      Director: [1.]--De Oliveira, Rogerio [2.]--Smith, Jo [3.]--Cullen, Colette
      Broadcast Standard: PAL
    - Title: What I Remember of What You Said, Screened: 1991; 119324 (Box 93, Folder ID: 143.1104)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6502
      Director: Guarino, Robin
    - Title: Hexe, 119323 (Box 93, Folder ID: 143.1105)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6503
      Director: Mulder, Anneke
      Duration: 180 minutes
    - Title: Mike's Film, Screened: 1990, 1996; 119322 (Box 93, Folder ID: 143.1106)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6504
      Director: Lamble, David
    - Title: State of Mind, Screened: 1993; 119321 (Box 93, Folder ID: 143.1107)
      Old number: 190, EII4f, V.12.6505
      Director: Black, Angie
    - Title: Safe Sane Consensual SM - A Documentary, 119320 (Box 93, Folder ID: 143.1108)
      Old number: 85, EII4f, V.12.6507
      Director: Roberts, Greg and Soucy-West, Ann
    - Title: Queer New World, 119319 (Box 93, Folder ID: 143.1109)
      Old number: 170, EII4f, V.12.6510
      Director: Smith, Vicky
    - Title: Voices of Life: People Living w/ AIDS, Screened: 1991; 119318 (Box 93, Folder ID: 143.1110)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6513
      Director: Wright, Patrick
    - Title: Waiting, 119317 (Box 93, Folder ID: 143.1111)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6515
    - Title: Chancleteras, 119316 (Box 93, Folder ID: 143.1112)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6517
      Director: Gatti, Jose
    - Title: Ash and Hatred, 119315 (Box 93, Folder ID: 143.1113)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6518
    - Title: What I Remember of What You Said, Screened: 1991; 119314 (Box 93, Folder ID: 143.1114)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6519.C2
    - Title: How Long Must I Wait For You?, 119313 (Box 93, Folder ID: 143.1115)
      Old number: 69, EII4f, V.12.6520
      Director: Klaus, Veronica
    - Title: DHPG Mon Amour, 119312 (Box 93, Folder ID: 143.1116)
      Old number: 57, EII4f, V.12.6522
      Director: George, Carl Michael
    - Title: Duree, 119311 (Box 93, Folder ID: 143.1117)
      Old number: 70, EII4f, V.12.6524
      Director: Motter, Robb
    - Title: Prisoners, 119310 (Box 93, Folder ID: 143.1118)
      Old number: 18, EII4f, V.12.6525
      Director: Motter, Robb and Carter, Chad
    - Title: zuJoBw, 119309 (Box 93, Folder ID: 143.1119)
      Old number: 92, EII4f, V.12.6527
      Director: Dougherty, Cecilia and Nobo, Monique
      Duration: 17 minutes
    - Title: None of the Above, Screened: 1994; 119308 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1120)
      Old number: 187, EII4f, V.12.6528
      Director: Fowler-Smith, Penny
    - Title: Myke's Cut: Gays in Military, 119307 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1121)
      Old number: EII3b, V.12.6536
      Distributor: distributed by: Femme Distribution
    - Title: Evil Thoughts, Screened: 1993; 119306 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1122)
      Old number: 246, EII3b, V.12.6538
      Director: Hoffman, Joe
    - Title: Biways, 119305 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1123)
      Old number: EII3b, V.12.6541
      Director: Shimazaki, Paul and Chow, Prescott
    - Title: Femme, 119304 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1124)
      Old number: EII3b, V.12.6542
    - Title: [1.]--Boobs/condoms [2.]--Bumps [3.]--My Dinner at Dan's [4.]--My Kind of Girl [5.]--Questions [6.]--Upsidedown [7.]--Spontaneous Evolution, [2, 3.]--Screened: 1993; 119303 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1125)
      Old number: 254, EII3b, V.12.6546
      Director: [2, 3.]--Carlton, Wendy Jo
    - Title: The Candy Tangerine, 119302 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1126)
      Old number: EII4c, V.12.6547
      Director: Horowitz, Jonathan
    - Title: [1.]--Little League [2.]--Distant Shore [3.]--Tales From the […] [4.]Touch Me [5.]--He Would Have Loved Me […], [5.]--Screened: 1993; 119301 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1127)
      Old number: EII3b, V.12.6549
      Director: Slater, John and Taylor, Mark
    - Title: [1.]--Edgar Barcus [2.]--A Simple Man [3.]--Victor [4.]--Charity Infractions [5.]--Hallucination Downtown [6.]--Red [J…] Picnic [7.]--The Alleged, [7.]--Screened: 1993; 119300 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1128)
      Old number: 253, EII3b, V.12.6550
      Director: [7.]--Slane, Andrea
    - Title: [1.]--Truck Driver With Wig [2.]--The Fading [3.]--The Dreaming, [3.]--Screened: 1993; 119299 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1129)
      Old number: K7b, V.12.8724
      Director: Thomas, Ifan
    - Title: [1.]--Finally Destroy Us [2.]--Nation [3.]--Womads [4.]--Darling Child [5.]--Skullfuck [6.]--Caress [7.]--Sunray [8.]--Watch Out For North Dakota [9.]--Put Your Lips Around Yes [10.]--Shred of Sex, [6, 8, 9]--Screened: 1993; 119298 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1130)
      Old number: K7b, V.12.8744
      Director: [1-4.]--Kalin, Tom [5.]--Kelly, Joe and Fass, Danny [6-9.]--Lindell, John [10.]--Snider, Greta
    - Title: Monzetu Donden-Gaesi, 119297 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1131)
      Old number: K7b, V.12.8745
      Director: Kumasiro, Dr. Tatumi
    - Title: We Are Not a Force To Be Taken Lightly, 119296 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1132)
      Old number: K7b, V.12.8748
    - Title: [1.]--Butterfly Potion [2.]--Dick Johnson [3.]--Lesbians of Russia, Jimmy [4.]--Little Fury Things, 119295 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1133)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8783
      Director: Spring, Jim and Jurgensen, Jens
    - Title: Voice, 119294 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1134)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8786
      Director: Turcotte, James
    - Title: M.M. In Motion, 119293 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1135)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8787
      Director: Ostrovsky, Vivian
    - Title: Family Diaries, 1969-75, 119292 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1136)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8789
    - Title: Mind is the Medium, 119291 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1137)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8790
      Director: Carman, James
    - Title: The Brenda and Glennda Show: [1.]--ACT-UP/Target Bush [2.]--Wigstock '91, Screened: 1992; 119290 (Box 94, Folder ID: 143.1138)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8795
      Director: [1.]--Wentzy, James
      Duration: 160 minutes
    - Title: AIDS Community Television: Target Bush, Screened: 1992; 119289 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1139)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8795.C2
      Director: Wentzy, James
    - Title: Mas'ter-ba-shen, 119288 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1140)
      Old number: 41, K7d, V.12.8796
      Director: Spitzer, John Eric
    - Title: Two Spirits Speak Out, 119287 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1141)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8797
    - Title: "Trajectoires et passages"": Women Filmmakers in the Avant-Garde - 1980-1990 [1.]--Grapholetti [2.]--Choreographie [3.]--Stories [4.]--USSA [5.]--Mansfield K. [6.]--IN/SIDE/OUT I-VI, [1.]--Screened: 1991 [6.]--Screened: 1988; 119286 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1142)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8798
      Director: [1.]--Thomas, Francoise [2.]--Thirache, Marcelle [3.]--Fontaine, Cecile [4.]--Ostrovsky, Vivian [5.]--Rousset, Martine [6.]--Burford, Jennifer
      Duration: 150 minutes
    - Title: Medea - A Girl Just Like You, 119285 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1143)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8800
      Director: Schicker, Eva
    - Title: [Russian title], 119284 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1144)
      Old number: 4, 49091, DIII 1C, V.12.8878
      Director: [Russian credits]
    - Title: Be Good, My Children, 119283 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1145)
      Old number: K7b, V.12.8986
      Director: Chang, Christine
    - Title: [1.]--Work-in-Progress [2.]--The Natural Order, 119282 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1146)
      Old number: EII3c, V.12.9101.C1
      Director: Mertes, Cara
    - Title: Bald Diva luv, Screened: 1993; 119281 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1147)
      Old number: V.12.9170
      Director: Johnson, Vanessa
      Distributor: performers: [listed on tape container]
      Duration: 5 minutes
    - Title: Homophobia Is Known To Cause Nightmares, Screened: 1993; 119280 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1148)
      Old number: EII3e, V.12.9171
      Director: Handelman, Michelle
    - Title: Together Alone, Screened: 1991; 119279 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1149)
      Old number: EII3e, V.12.9175
      Director: Castellaneta, P.J.
    - Title: Smoke, 119278 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1150)
      Old number: EII3f, V.12.9192
      Director: D'Auria, Mark
    - Title: Tomboychik, Screened: 1993; 119277 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1151)
      Old number: EII3a, V.12.9219
      Director: DuBowski, Sandi
    - Title: [1.]--Mary Magdaline [2.]--L'Amour Fou, [2.]--Screened: 1992; 119276 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1152)
      Old number: EII3a, V.12.9220
      Director: Serra, M.M.
    - Title: [1.]--The Dreaming [2.]--Man Act/Sweatlodge [3.]--Step We Gaily [4.]--Amelia Rose Towers [5.]--Against the Inhuman Undershadow of the Lynch Mob, [1, 3, 4, 5.]--Screened: 1993; 119275 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1153, E-records fales_mss143, E-records 143.1153)
      Old number: EII4d, V.34U.6401
      Director: [1.]--Thomas, Ifan [3.]--Broadbent, Lucinda [4.]--Farkas, Jackie [5.]--De Oliveira, Rogerio
      Format: 3/4 in. Umatic
      Duration: 00:61:00
    - Title: Voi Che Sapete, Screened: 1993; 119274 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1154)
      Old number: EII4b, V.34U.6403
      Duration: [5 minutes]
    - Title: Sleeplessness, 119273 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1155)
      Old number: EII4b, V.34U.6404
    - Title: Find Your G Spot: [How] To Female Ejaculate, 119272 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1156)
      Old number: EII4b, V.34U.6405
      Director: Murphy, Melissa
    - Title: Waves of a Distant Shore, 119271 (Box 95, Folder ID: 143.1157)
      Old number: EII4b, V.34U.6407
      Director: Ong, Meng
    - Title: The New Dark Ages, Screened: 1993; 119270 (Box 96, Folder ID: 143.1158)
      Old number: EII4b, V.34U.6408
      Director: Tomasino, Walter and Giuliano, Steven
    - Title: [1.]--No Money, No Honey [2.]--Lovin' In My Oven [3.]--Cholita in No Controles [4.]--That Fertile Feeling [5.]--It All Started In Black, [4.]--Screened: 1995; 119269 (Box 96, Folder ID: 143.1159)
      Old number: EII4b, V.34U.6409
      Director: O'Shea, John [4.]--Davis, Vaginal Crème
    - Title: Lilies, Screened: 1993; 119268 (Box 96, Folder ID: 143.1160)
      Old number: EII4b, V.34U.6410
      Director: O'Malley, John
    - Title: Video Boyfriend, 119267 (Box 96, Folder ID: 143.1161)
      Old number: EII4b, V.34U.6414
      Director: Ellis, Andrew
    - Title: Theory on a Stick, 119266 (Box 96, Folder ID: 143.1162)
      Old number: V.34U.6415
      Director: Murrah, Natalie
    - Title: Little League Lee, 119265 (Box 96, Folder ID: 143.1163)
      Old number: EII4d, V.34U.6460
      Director: Gerstein, Lee
    - Title: Light on the Path, 119264 (Box 96, Folder ID: 143.1164)
      Old number: EII4d, V.34U.6458
      Distributor: distributed by: Motus Film and Video
    - Title: [1.]--Kachapati (Spray the Wall) [2.]--The Pervert Explores An Instant, [2.]--Screened: 1993; 119263 (Box 96, Folder ID: 143.1165)
      Old number: EII4d, V.34U.6459
      Director: Wright, Georgia B.
    - Title: [1.]--Boobs [2.]--Condoms Are A Girl's Best Friend, 119262 (Box 96, Folder ID: 143.1166)
      Old number: 198, EII4d, V.34U.6461
    - Title: Our Fanzine Friends Part 1, 119261 (Box 96, Folder ID: 143.1167)
      Old number: EII4d, V.34U.6463 1/2
    - Title: Our Fanzine Friends Part 2: [1.]--Spring Break [2.]--Streetwalker Fashion/Fertile Latoya Jackson Video Mag, [2.]--Screened: 1993; 119260 (Box 96, Folder ID: 143.1168)
      Old number: EII4d, V.34U.6463 2/2
      Director: [2.]--Castro, Rick
      Distributor: performers: [2.]--[listed in 1993 program, includes Vaginal Davis]
    - Title: The Ideal/Na(rra)tion, 119259 (Box 97, Folder ID: 143.1169)
      Old number: K7c, V.34U.8754
      Director: Ching, Yau
    - Title: Drawing the Line, 119258 (Box 97, Folder ID: 143.1170)
      Old number: K7c, V.34.8755
      Director: Boschman, Lorna
    - Title: [1.]--The Language Of Boys [2.]--A Gorme's Delight, 119257 (Box 97, Folder ID: 143.1171)
      Old number: EII3c, V.34U.9122.C1
      Director: Christopher, Mark
    - Title: The Salt Mines, 119256 (Box 97, Folder ID: 143.1172)
      Old number: EII3d, V.34.9140.C1
      Director: Aikin, Susana and Aparicio, Carlos
    - Title: Postcards From America, 119255 (Box 97, Folder ID: 143.1173)
      Old number: EII3e, V.34.9160.C1
    - Title: Edit Master / Gay and Lesbian Experimental Film Program Fanzine Pt. 1, 119254 (Box 97, Folder ID: 143.1174)
      Old number: EII3f, V.34.9176
    - Title: Pt. 2 Fanzine Master [1.]--Spring Break [2.]--Streetwalker, 119253 (Box 97, Folder ID: 143.1175)
      Old number: EII3f, V.34U.9177
      Distributor: distributed by: Valkhn Film and Video, Inc.
    - Title: Strut, 119252 (Box 97, Folder ID: 143.1176)
      Old number: 51949, EII3f, V.34U.9178
      Director: DeRuiter, Heidi
    - Title: Medea -- Just A Girl Like You, 119251 (Box 97, Folder ID: 143.1177)
      Old number: EII3f, V.34.9188
    - Title: Palingenesis, 119250 (Box 97, Folder ID: 143.1178)
      Old number: EII3a, V.34U.9214
      Director: Martinez, Juan Carlos
    - Title: Sex Wars [1.]--I Am A Man, But… [2.]--He-She-Pee [3.]--Mr. Wonderful, [3.]--Screened: 1995; 119249 (Box 97, Folder ID: 143.1179)
      Old number: EII3a, V.34U.9216
      Director: [3.]--Malkames, Marlise
    - Title: [1.]--Requiem [2.]--Spin Cycle [3.]--Fag Solos, Screened: [1993] [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53] [2.]--Screened: 1991; 119248 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1258)
      Old number: EII4e, V.12.6487
      Director: [2.]--Burch, Aarin
      Format: EII4e, V.12.6487
    - Title: Tucumcari Tonite, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119247 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1259)
      Old number: EII4e, V.12.6489, 248
      Director: Benson, Suzanne
      Format: EII4e, V.12.6489, 248
    - Title: Bill and Ted's Homosexual Adventure, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119246 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1260)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6499.C2, 68
      Distributor: performers: Pansy Division
      Format: EII4f, V.12.6499.C2, 68
    - Title: Stroke of Luck, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119245 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1261)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6508, 302
      Director: Steffen, James
      Format: EII4f, V.12.6508, 302
    - Title: EII4f V.12.6509 [case only, no videocassette], 119244 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1262)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6509
      Format: EII4f, V.12.6509
      Duration: N/A
    - Title: At Home With the Stars, Screened: 1990, [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119243 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1263)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6516
      Director: Westmoreland, Joe
      Format: EII4f, V.12.6516
    - Title: Trojans: A Mind Over Motter Video, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119242 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1264)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6521, 77
      Format: EII4f, V.12.6521, 77
    - Title: Mercury Rising, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119241 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1265)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6523, 97
      Director: Manson, Portia
      Format: EII4f, V.12.6523, 97
    - Title: My Livingroom is a Theatre, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119240 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1266)
      Old number: EII4f, V.12.6526, 103
      Director: Prietzel, Claudia
      Format: EII4f, V.12.6526, 103
    - Title: My Courbet…Or, A Beaver's Tale, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119239 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1267)
      Old number: EII3b, V.12.6535, 235
      Director: Patten, Mary
      Format: EII3b, V.12.6535, 235
    - Title: [1.]--Sensual Men [2.]--Soapy Water, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119238 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1268)
      Old number: EII3b, V.12.6539, 244
      Director: Bailer,N. Lee and Glowienke, Kurt
      Distributor: performers: [listed on accompanying letter]
      Format: EII3b, V.12.6539, 244
    - Title: [1.]--Girls Will Be Boys [2.]--Jill Jacks Off, [1.]--Screened: 1993. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119237 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1269)
      Old number: EII3b, V.12.6540
      Director: [1.]-- Kuhne, Kadet and Texas Tomboy
      Format: EII3b, V.12.6540
    - Title: Private Pleasures, Screened: 1993. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119236 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1270)
      Old number: EII3b, V.12.6543
      Director: Wow, O.
      Format: EII3b, V.12.6543
    - Title: Peanut, Screened: 1993. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119235 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1271)
      Old number: K7b, V.12.8728, 121
      Director: Jacobsen, Rick
      Format: K7b, V.12.8728, 121
    - Title: The Brenda And Glennda Show: Gender Cruise on the Circle Line - Part 2, Screened: 1993. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119234 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1272)
      Old number: K7d, V.12.8794
      Format: K7d, V.12.8794
    - Title: Kiev Blue, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119233 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1273)
      Old number: EII3c, V.12.9100.C1
      Director: MacDonald, Heather
      Format: EII3c, V.12.9100.C1
    - Title: Lesbian and Gay Films and Videos From Brasil, 119232 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1274)
      Old number: EII3e, V.12.9172
      Director: Cypriano, Tania
      Format: EII3e, V.12.9172
    - Title: Voices From the Front, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119231 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1275)
      Old number: EII3e, V.12.9174
      Director: Hutt, Robyn, Elgear, Sandra and Meieran, David
      Distributor: performers: [listed in 1991 program]
      Format: EII3e, V.12.9174
    - Title: Down On The River, Screened: 1991 [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119230 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1276)
      Old number: EII4c, V.34U.6416, 145
      Director: Stevens, Ylonda
      Format: EII4c, V.34U.6416, 145
    - Title: [1.]--Conceicao [2.]--Concepcion, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119229 (Box 98, Folder ID: 143.1277)
      Old number: EII4c, V.34U.6417.C2
      Format: EII4c, V.34U.6417.C2
    - Title: Avid Tutorial Sample Footage, 119228 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1239)
      Old number:
      Format: Betacam SP
    - Title: MIX Trailer 1993, Screened: [1993]; 119227 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1240)
    - Title: Waking Up To Rape, 119226 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1241)
      Old number: 6
      Duration: 40 minutes
    - Title: The Dreaming, Screened: 1993; 119225 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1244)
    - Title: Figment, 119224 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1247)
      Old number: 7360
      Director: Sharits, Paul
      Format: Betacam
    - Title: Figment, 119223 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1248)
      Old number: 7361
    - Title: Strut, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119222 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1249)
      Old number: EII4b, V.12.6393, 306
    - Title: Deep Inside Porn Stars, Screened: 1993. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119221 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1250)
      Old number: EII4c, V.12.6426,
      Director: Club 90
      Distributor: performers: [listed in 1993 program]
    - Title: In Your Face With Amazing Grace (The Vatican is Burning), Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119220 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1251)
      Old number: EII4c, V.12.6437
    - Title: Mrs. Mouth Video Profile, Screened: 1993. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119219 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1252)
      Old number: EII4c, V.12.6438
      Director: Silverzweig, Paul
    - Title: American Fabulous, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119218 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1253)
      Old number: EII4d, V.12.6446
      Director: Dakota, Reno
    - Title: Poof, Screened: 1994. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119217 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1254)
      Old number: EII4d, V.12.6455
      Director: Luketic, Robert
    - Title: The Cove Method, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119216 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1255)
      Old number: EII4e, V.12.6486
      Director: Higginbottom, Mrs. and Westmorely, Joe
    - Title: Into The Light, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119215 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1256)
      Old number: EII4e, V.12.6473, 55
    - Title: Butterfly Scavenger, Screened: [1993]. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119214 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1257)
      Old number: V.12.6486, 4
      Director: Morse, Barry
    - Title: Tales From the Watercloset, Screened: 1993. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119213 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1278)
      Old number: EII4c, V.34U.6419
      Director: Walsh, Susan and Marciniak, Kris
    - Title: Midwest Mambo, Screened: 1993. [more yellow tape in boxes 47-53]; 119212 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1279)
      Old number: EII4d, V.34U.6456.C2
      Director: Everly, Bart
    - Title: A Hard Reign's Gonna Fall, 119211 (Box 99, Folder ID: 143.1280)
      Director: Lance, Dean
    - Title: Fire!, 119210 (Box 100, Folder ID: 143.1217)
      Director: Frilot-Harris
    - Title: Suburban Dykes, Screened: [1990]; 119209 (Box 100, Folder ID: 143.1483)
      Director: Fatale
      Duration: [30] minutes
    - Title: AGORA, Screened: 1992; 119208 (Box 100, Folder ID: 143.1487)
      Old number: 50
      Director: Kinney, Robert and Donald
    - Title: BurLEZk II, Screening: Unknown; 119207 (Box 100, Folder ID: 143.1515)
    - Title: Una Vuelta / A Ride Out, Screened: Unknown; 119206 (Box 100, Folder ID: 143.1568)
      Director: Montoya, Ivonne Patricia
    - Title: Mein ist Dein Ganzes Herz, Screened: Unknown; 119205 (Box 100, Folder ID: 143.1688)
      Old number: v.12.6480 E II 4 e 30
      Director: Gotz, Elke
    - Title: DeAundra Peek, Screened: Unknown; 119204 (Box 100, Folder ID: 143.1720)
    - Title: [1.]-- Au Revoir, Shirlei [2.]-- Viva Eu!, Screened: Unknown; 119203 (Box 100, Folder ID: 143.1740)
      Old number: 4C
    - Title: "Hunting Season", Screened: 1990, 1996; 119202 (Box 100, Folder ID: 143.1741)
      Old number: 4B
    - Title: [1.]-- The Earring [2.]-- Dyke After Dyke [3.]-- No Mirror [4.]-- Chancleteras, Screened: Unknown; 119201 (Box 100, Folder ID: 143.1742)
      Old number: 4A
    - Title: [1.]-- Darkness of my Language [2.]-- Amorae [3.]-- Dyke After Dyke [3.]-- The Second Beast, Screened: Unknown; 119200 (Box 100, Folder ID: 143.1743)
      Old number: 4D
    - Title: Ciudades de Lujuria (Cities of Lust), Screened: 1993; 119199 (Box 100, Folder ID: 143.1472)
    - Title: [1.]-- Diversion [2.]-- Song of the Goddess, Screened: [1993]; 119198 (Box 100, Folder ID: 143.1605)
      Old number: 15
      Director: Pau, Ellen
      Duration: [60] minutes
    - Title: Ego Beach, Screened: [1993]; 119197 (Box 100, Folder ID: 143.1643)
      Old number: 5
      Director: Kuhne, Lisa
    - Title: [1.]-- Kissy Suzuki Sucks [2.]-- No Glove / No Love [3.]-- And It's in Colour [4.]-- Inner Circle [5.]-- Pout Safer Sex TV Dinner, Screened: Unknown; 119196 (Box 100, Folder ID: 143.1649)
    - Title: [1.]--The Last Time [2.]--Home You Go [3.]--Secrets, Screened: [1993]; 119195 (Box 101, Folder ID: 143.1297)
      Old number: 498
      Director: Allen, Colette
    - Title: Shadows, Screened: 1993; 119194 (Box 101, Folder ID: 143.1298)
      Director: Caerage and Teri
    - Title: Quasi Una Fantasia, Screened: [1993]; 119193 (Box 101, Folder ID: 143.1299)
      Director: Muller, Paul
    - Title: Greetings From Africa, Screened: [1993]; 119192 (Box 101, Folder ID: 143.1301)
      Director: Dunye, Cheryl
    - Title: Anthology Film Archives Preservation Dinner Feb. 2, 1993, 119191 (Box 101, Folder ID: 143.1302)
      Director: Beroes, Stephanie
    - Title: [1.]--The Serenade [2.]--L'Ile de la Sagesse [3.]--[Imer?]telle, [2.]--Screened: 1993; 119190 (Box 101, Folder ID: 143.1303)